Hi, I'm Donna. I manage a large marketing team here in California and I'm a
mother of three beautiful kids, one with special needs and I really wanted to
share the results of working with Shree. Managing a big team can sometimes be
challenging with deadlines, handling various projects, managing my little kids,
can sometimes be overwhelming. Needless to say I was stressed out and having
panic attacks which affected my health and my bond with my kids. I was fortunate
to meet Shree who was able to get into the root cause that was rooted in my
childhood and growing years. We were able to shift it almost instantly and
the difference was night and day because I became more calm and peaceful my
efficiency and performance at work went up. My team recognized the change very
quickly and I am able to have a much deeper bond with my kids which is
priceless. Shree I can't thank you enough for your love and care and for helping me
hope a lot of people get to experience your magic. Thank you so much.